HỒI TƯỞNG
DỪNG LẠI
Hachikuji Mayoi
Hoạt Cảnh số      22
X-Ray image
Even closer
Araragi's inner thoughts / grumbling
Hoạt Cảnh số      47
Araraunchy
Hoạt Cảnh số      52
SHOCKED
Hoạt Cảnh số      58
Khung Hình Đỏ
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Khung Hình Đen
Khung Hình Trắng
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
No surmounting your taste
Hoạt Cảnh số      77
No accounting for taste
Hoạt Cảnh số      78
Back to the topic
Hoạt Cảnh số      79
They were cat ears.
A pair of cute cat ears
protruded from Hanekawa's little head.
I stood silent, biting my lower lip.
So hard it started bleeding.
Don't laugh.
I just acted serious in getting her to do this,
so I can't laugh.
Delivering a moving speech to convince
someone to do something and then bursting with laughter
and making a fool of them when they actually do it is
a common manga cliche,
Delivering a moving speech to convince
someone to do something and then bursting with laughter
and making a fool of them when they actually do it is
a common manga cliche,
Delivering a moving speech to convince
someone to do something and then bursting with laughter
and making a fool of them when they actually do it is
a common manga cliche,
Delivering a moving speech to convince
someone to do something and then bursting with laughter
and making a fool of them when they actually do it is
a common manga cliche,
Delivering a moving speech to convince
someone to do something and then bursting with laughter
and making a fool of them when they actually do it is
a common manga cliche,
Delivering a moving speech to convince
someone to do something and then bursting with laughter
and making a fool of them when they actually do it is
a common manga cliche,
Delivering a moving speech to convince
someone to do something and then bursting with laughter
and making a fool of them when they actually do it is
a common manga cliche,
Delivering a moving speech to convince
someone to do something and then bursting with laughter
and making a fool of them when they actually do it is
a common manga cliche,
Delivering a moving speech to convince
someone to do something and then bursting with laughter
and making a fool of them when they actually do it is
a common manga cliche,
Delivering a moving speech to convince
someone to do something and then bursting with laughter
and making a fool of them when they actually do it is
a common manga cliche,
Delivering a moving speech to convince
someone to do something and then bursting with laughter
and making a fool of them when they actually do it is
a common manga cliche,
Delivering a moving speech to convince
someone to do something and then bursting with laughter
and making a fool of them when they actually do it is
a common manga cliche,
but I've sworn never
to do something like that.
Still, these cat ears...
They suit Hanekawa really well,
as if they were tailor-made
to go along with her neat,
straight bangs.
They suit Hanekawa really well,
as if they were tailor-made
to go along with her neat,
straight bangs.
They suit Hanekawa really well,
as if they were tailor-made
to go along with her neat,
straight bangs.
They suit Hanekawa really well,
as if they were tailor-made
to go along with her neat,
straight bangs.
They suit Hanekawa really well,
as if they were tailor-made
to go along with her neat,
straight bangs.
They suit Hanekawa really well,
as if they were tailor-made
to go along with her neat,
straight bangs.
They suit Hanekawa really well,
as if they were tailor-made
to go along with her neat,
straight bangs.
They suit Hanekawa really well,
as if they were tailor-made
to go along with her neat,
straight bangs.
A thought I first had during Golden Week came back to me:
She'd been born to wear a pair of cat ears
on her head someday...
That said.
During the Golden Week nightmare,
it was never Hanekawa as herself with cat ears—
so that's why her present look
was blowing me away.
Subordinate
Body
Ah, I see. This time the cat ears are black ,
the same color as her hair.
Phông chữ dùng cho minh hoạ: Gentium Basic và VL DellaRobbia BT
Mèo Tsubasa, Phần 2
Tập Mười Ba
Bicycle parking
Students Only
Gymnasium
New email
Hanekawa Tsubasa
1 new
Voice Actress: Saitou Chiwa
(Works for I'm Enterprise)
Born in Saitama Prefecture. Voices strong-willed women,
weak women, lively girls and even boys.
Has also voiced animals, non-human characters,
eccentric roles that speek in an low voice,
and other types of characters too.
Hoạt Cảnh số      125
Snow Slake
Snowslake
Park
Snow Slake
P
a
r
k
Khung Hình Đen
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
THỜI KHOÁ BIỂU NĂM BA TRƯỜNG THPT NAOETSU
Unpleasant
calculations
Hoạt Cảnh số      157
Khung Hình Đen
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Headaches
Hoạt Cảnh số      177
Hoạt Cảnh số      179
Headaches
HỒI TƯỞNG
Oddities
Hoạt Cảnh số      194
(MÈO)
Hoạt Cảnh số      207
May twenty-seventh,
during the radio show
Hoạt Cảnh số      155
Live Action
Postcard
Hoạt Cảnh số      210
Live Action
Postcard
ZOOMED IN
Big Bear Cat
Hoạt Cảnh số      219
Panda = Big Bear Cat
Live Action
Postcard
Hoạt Cảnh số      222
Pretending to practice my putt
Hoạt Cảnh số      225
Live Action
Postcard
Hoạt Cảnh số      227
Thanks
Hoạt Cảnh số      280
Both were for you
Hoạt Cảnh số      286
Khung Hình Đỏ
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
A pair of breasts
Hoạt Cảnh số      295
Khung Hình Đỏ
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Vampire
Weight crab
Lost cow
Monkey's paw
Serpent
Senjougahara
Hitagi
Hachikuji
Mayoi
Kanbaru
Suruga
Sengoku
Nadeko
Hanekawa
Tsubasa
I don't know anything
Hoạt Cảnh số      321
Khung Hình Đen
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Curse Cat
Hoạt Cảnh số      348
Mèo
Mèo Tsubasa, Phần 3
Yêu Ma Quái Truyện
Còn Nữa
Kỳ Tới
Mèo Tsubasa, Phần 4