Khung Hình Đen
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Hoạt Cảnh số      4
Love
Single kanji A
Hoạt Cảnh số      4
Love
Single kanji A
Hoạt Cảnh số      4
Love
Single kanji A
Love is something to be stolen without hesitation.
Hoạt Cảnh số      4
Khung Hình Xanh
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
But.
Hoạt Cảnh số      8
Solemn
Khung Hình Vàng
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Not everyone is capable of that.
Hoạt Cảnh số      10
Hoạt Cảnh số      14
Khung Hình Đen
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
FIGURE
TRI
ANGLE
Hoạt Cảnh số      25
Anger
Buildup
Restraint
Đời
Thực
Hoạt Cảnh số      31
Khung Hình Đen
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Her headaches didn't stop at all
Hoạt Cảnh số      33
They only got worse and worse
Hoạt Cảnh số      36
Hoạt Cảnh số      38
Disorder
Single kanji B
Hoạt Cảnh số      38
Disorder
Single kanji B
Hoạt Cảnh số      38
Disorder
Single kanji B
I feel sick.
Hoạt Cảnh số      38
What have I done?
Hoạt Cảnh số      41
FIGURE
TRI
ANGLE
FIGURE
TRI
ANGLE
But I had no way of knowing. If Hanekawa...
Hoạt Cảnh số      48
If that girl decided to hide her true feelings,
even Senjōgahara wouldn't be able to tell.
Hoạt Cảnh số      51
Đời
Thực
Hoạt Cảnh số      51
Pressure
Single kanji C
Hoạt Cảnh số      51
Pressure
Single kanji C
But...
Hoạt Cảnh số      51
Dense, huh.
Hoạt Cảnh số      52
So her plans after graduation, too...
Oshino must have had some influence on her,
but you could also look at it as Hanekawa Tsubasa's
epic journey of heartbreak.
So her plans after graduation, too...
Oshino must have had some influence on her,
but you could also look at it as Hanekawa Tsubasa's
epic journey of heartbreak.
And she started having headaches too,
right after we talked about our plans.
Hoạt Cảnh số      52
And,
Hoạt Cảnh số      56
Đời
Thực
That time she closed her eyes and tried to kiss me...
Hoạt Cảnh số      58
Khung Hình Đỏ
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Original Story by Nisio Isin
Tập Mười Lăm
Yêu Ma Quái Truyện
Khung Hình Đỏ
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Phông chữ dùng cho minh hoạ: Gentium Basic và VL DellaRobbia BT
Mèo Tsubasa, Phần 5
Tập Mười Lăm
Hoạt Cảnh số      62
Kawa
Single kanji D
Hoạt Cảnh số      62
Kawa
Single kanji D
Hoạt Cảnh số      62
Hanekawa Tsubasa is a very important person to me.
Tập Cuối
Hoạt Cảnh số      68
Obey
Single kanji E
Hoạt Cảnh số      68
Obey
Single kanji E
Hoạt Cảnh số      68
Obey
Single kanji E
Hoạt Cảnh số      68
Spring break
Từ Tập 1, Hoạt Cảnh số 25
HỒI TƯỞNG
Từ Tập 1, Hoạt Cảnh số 54
Từ Tập 1, Hoạt Cảnh số 59
HỒI TƯỞNG
Khung Hình Đen
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Từ Tập 5, Hoạt Cảnh số 233
HỒI TƯỞNG
Khung Hình Tím
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Hoạt Cảnh số      80
When it happened, Hanekawa...
Was happy for me.
Hoạt Cảnh số      80
That's what I thought
Hoạt Cảnh số      82
Hoạt Cảnh số      84
But...
That must have been a lie too.
Hoạt Cảnh số      86
I've never told a lie
And now, a performance by Gekidan Inu Curry
Hoạt Cảnh số      93
End of performance
Hoạt Cảnh số      94
Khung Hình Đen
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Hoạt Cảnh số      109
Embryo
29th day
Hoạt Cảnh số      113
Back to the belly
Cảnh Mới cho Hoạt Cảnh số 130 Tập 15
HỒI TƯỞNG
Hoạt Cảnh số      131
Connection
Single kanji F
Hoạt Cảnh số      131
Connection
Single kanji F
Hoạt Cảnh số      131
You're wrong, Hachikuji
Yes,
Hoạt Cảnh số      135
I love everything.
There's nothing I don't love about her.
Hoạt Cảnh số      144
Denial / Voice / Dialogue
Hoạt Cảnh số      147
Hoạt Cảnh số      148
Từ Tập 1, Hoạt Cảnh số 20
HỒI TƯỞNG
Khung Hình Đỏ
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
FIGURE
TRI
ANGLE
FIGURE
TRI
ANGLE
Hoạt Cảnh số      158
Khung Hình Đỏ
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Cua
Ốc Sên
Khỉ
Rắn
Mèo
Khung Hình Đen
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
It was a lie.
Hoạt Cảnh số      190
One of those lies she supposedly never told.
Hoạt Cảnh số      191
A painful wish.
Khung Hình Đen
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Mèo Tsubasa
Tập Năm
Begin
Hoạt Cảnh số      225
Đời
Thực
Oddity
Solemn
Khung Hình Đỏ
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Từ Tập 11, Hoạt Cảnh số 263
HỒI TƯỞNG
Khung Hình Đen
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Hoạt Cảnh số      260
Kill
I'll be absolutely sure to kill you.
Hoạt Cảnh số      260
ABSOLUTELY SURE.
Khung Hình Đỏ
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Khung Hình Đen
Hitagi
Hoạt Cảnh số      272
Khung Hình Đỏ
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Khung Hình Đen
Mayoi
Hoạt Cảnh số      299
Suruga
Hoạt Cảnh số      306
Hoạt Cảnh số      308
Nadeko
Ripples
Hoạt Cảnh số      315
For example, if I died
Hoạt Cảnh số      320
Oshino Shinobu
Khung Hình Vàng
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Hoạt Cảnh số      343
Black Hanekawa / Flashback / Voice-only
Khung Hình Đen
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
GRAND CULTURAL FESTIVAL
Khung Hình Đen
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Hitagi
Hoạt Cảnh số      432
Khung Hình Đen
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Koyomi /
Monologue /
Dialogue
Koyomi /
Monologue /
Dialogue
Hoạt Cảnh số      475
Khung Hình Đen
Hoạt Cảnh số      Không Có
Khung Hình Đỏ
Mèo
Mèo Tsubasa, Phần 5
Yêu Ma Quái Truyện
Và thế là...
Hết